catapultsystems.com 2019-07-23

# Catapult Systems Privacy Policy - Catapult Systems

### INTRODUCTION

Catapult Systems respects your privacy and recognizes your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information you choose to provide us. Catapult Systems has established this Privacy and Cookie Policy so that you may better understand the purpose for which we collect and use personal information.  
Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a physical address, an email address, or other contact information including, gender, occupation, personal interests, or other similar information.

### WHY WE ASK YOU TO SHARE PERSONAL DATA

The purposes and reasons for processing your personal data are included, but not limited to:

  * Buying Catapult Systems solutions and services
  * Receiving information about Catapult Systems solutions, services, and events
  * Participating in Catapult Systems online communities, including our blog, social media channels/pages
  * Storing your preferences for future interactions and communications from Catapult Systems
  * Resolving customer service issues or other service/solution complaints
  * Helping us to improve solutions and services
  * Creating campaigns that are designed to benefit you, allowing us to optimize customer service
  * Receiving personalized messages, special offers and advertisements that are relevant to your personal interests, based on the information you have shared with us and on the information we have collected through cookies regarding your use of the Catapult Systems website/social media/blogs. For more information on how we use cookies, see our Cookie Clause below.

### TYPES OF DATA WE MAY COLLECT

When you interact with Catapult Systems, for instance by signing up for our blog, purchasing a solution/service or interacting with Catapult Systems via social media, e.g. “like us on Facebook,” we may ask for or receive certain data, such as:

  * Your name
  * Your email address
  * Your telephone number
  * Your social media profile
  * Your gender
  * Your age
  * Information about the products and services you have purchased
  * Your usage of and activities on our social media pages
  * Your interests
  * Other information related to your online behavior

Also, depending on the choices you have made regarding your settings on various social media sites, certain personal data may be shared with Catapult Systems about your online activities and social media profiles, e.g. interests, marital status, gender, user name, photo, comments you have posted, etc.  
In addition, we may collect personal data via cookies or similar techniques, including, but not limited to:

  * Your IP address
  * Your cookie ID
  * Your web browser
  * Your location
  * The web pages you visit on our websites
  * The advertisements you’ve viewed or clicked through
  * Etc.

When you interact with Catapult Systems on behalf of a business customer, supplier, or business partner of Catapult Systems, we may collect:

  * Your name
  * Your email address
  * Your telephone number
  * Your IP address
  * Your business address
  * Name and address of the company you work for

### HOW WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL DATA

  * Contacting us offline via courier, ground mail, telephone, email, or facsimile and providing any personal data
  * Requesting information about our solutions or services via one of our website form
  * Registering for an in-person event or webinar
  * Ordering a solution or service; signing a statement of work
  * Registering for an online account or a mobile application
  * Subscribing to a Catapult Systems blog
  * Cookies placed on your computer or mobile device when visiting our website
  * Social listening: Catapult Systems may search the internet for relevant and publicly available content and use it to improve its products and services, resolve consumer issues, and provide targeted marketing

### USE OF COOKIES ON OUR WEBSITE

A ‘cookie’ is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored on the user’s computer by the user’s web browser while the user is browsing. When you visit a site that uses cookies for the first time, a cookie is downloaded onto your computer/mobile device so that the next time you visit that site, your device will remember useful information such as visited pages, information you that were interested in, or your login options.

Catapult Systems uses cookies to help you get the most out of Catapult Systems solutions and services. In order to manage your cookie preferences, you may alter the cookie settings in your browser settings at any time. If you do disable cookies in your browser settings, you will find that you will not be permitted to enter our website. This will occur across all affiliated Catapult Systems sites.

 _ **Can a website user block cookies?**_

Yes. As explained below, under Managing Cookies, you can disable our cookies on www.catapultsystems.com. However, please be aware that this will reduce the functionality of our website. Please remember that if you do choose to disable cookies, you may find that certain sections of our website do not work properly.

### HOW TO MANAGE COOKIES

As we explain in our Cookie Policy, cookies help you to get the most out of our websites. If you do disable our cookies you may find that certain sections of our website will not work. For example, you may have difficulties logging in or viewing certain information about our products. Unless you disable our cookies, your continued use of our website will be considered to be your consent to our use of cookies on this device in accordance with our cookie policy. For detailed steps on how to enable or disable cookies using your browser, refer to the links below:

All other browsers: Please look for a “help” function in the browser or contact the browser provider. Additional Information about Third-Party CookiesUsers based in the European Union can visit www.youronlinechoices.eu and users based in the United States can visit www.aboutads.info/choices to opt out of third-party cookies.

### USE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA

Catapult Systems takes privacy and security very seriously and strives to put our website users first in all aspects of our business. We will never disclose, share, or sell your data without your consent, unless required to do so by law.

Catapult Systems will only retain your data for as long as necessary and for the purposes specified in this notice. We have strict review and retention policies in place to meet these obligations. If you may be a customer, we may be required under United States Federal laws to keep your basic personal data (name, address, contact details) for a minimum of 6 years after which time it will be destroyed.

The Catapult Systems website is not generally targeted toward anyone under the age of 18, and we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age on our website. Our solutions, services, and events are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

We do not automatically enroll you, or “opt you into” any marketing or mailing lists. Rather, when you express an interest in our solutions or services, we will ask you to confirm your consent freely and expressly in order that we may then contact you.

Again, we will only contact you, after you have first expressed your consent to learn more about our solutions or services that you have expressed interest in.  
Processing for any purpose other than those specified in this policy is strictly prohibited. All interactions with you occur following your consent, which you are free to withdraw at any time.

### THIRD PARTIES

  * Catapult Systems will not transfer your personal information to third parties without your consent, except under the following limited conditions:
  * We have your consent to share the information
  * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested or contractually agreed to
  * We need to transmit the information to third parties who work on behalf of Catapult Systems to provide a product or service to you, in which cases we will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the product or service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose
  * As part of a merger or sale of business
  * As required by law or to respond to legal processes or lawful requests, including law enforcement or government agencies

 **The third-party processors/controllers that we work with include the following:**

 **Microsoft Corporation**  
• Corporate Address: One Microsoft Way, Redmond, WA 98052  
• Data Privacy Contact: [buscond@microsoft.com](mailto:buscond@microsoft.com)  
• Privacy Policy  
• Purpose for Processing: Consent, Performance of a Contract, Legitimate Interests

 **Consensus**  
• Corporate Address: 7984 S 1300 E, Sandy, UT 84094  
• Data Privacy Contact: [info@goconsensus.com](mailto:info@goconsensus.com)  
• [Privacy Policy](https://www.goconsensus.com/privacy-policy/)  
• Purpose for Processing: Consent, Performance of a Contract, Legitimate Interests

 **Calendly**  
• Corporate Address: 1315 Peachtree St NE, Atlanta, GA 30309  
• Data Privacy Contact: [support@calendly.com](mailto:support@calendly.com)  
• [Privacy Policy](https://calendly.com/pages/privacy)  
• Purpose for Processing: Consent, Performance of a Contract, Legitimate Interests

 **Wistia**  
• Corporate Address: 17 Tudor Street, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 02139 USA  
• Data Privacy Contact: [privacy@wistia.com](mailto:privacy@wistia.com)  
• [Privacy Policy](https://wistia.com/privacy)  
• Purpose for Processing: Performance of a Contract, Legitimate Interests

 **Unbounce**  
• Corporate Address: 400-401 West Georgia Street, Vancouver, BC, Canada, V6B 5A1  
• Data Privacy Contact: [support@unbounce.com](mailto:support@unbounce.com)  
• [Privacy Policy](https://unbounce.com/privacy/)  
• Purpose for Processing: Performance of a Contract, Legitimate Interests

 **Marketo**  
• Corporate Address: 901 Mariners Island Blvd, Suite 500, San Mateo, CA 94404  
• Data Privacy Contact: [privacyofficer@marketo.com](mailto:privacyofficer@marketo.com)  
• [Privacy Policy](https://documents.marketo.com/legal/privacy/)  
• Purpose for Processing: Consent, Performance of a Contract, Legitimate Interest

 **ReadyTalk**  
• Corporate Address: 1900 16th Street, Suite 600, Denver, CO 80202  
• Data Privacy Contact: [GDPR@ReadyTalk.com](mailto:gdpr@readytalk.com)  
• [Privacy Policy](https://www.readytalk.com/privacy-statement)  
• Purpose for Processing: Consent, Performance of a Contract, Legitimate Interest

### YOUR RIGHTS

You have the right to access any personal information that Catapult Systems holds or processes about you and you may request information about:

  * What personal data we hold
  * The purposes of the processing
  * The categories of personal data concerned
  * The recipients to whom the personal data has/will be disclosed
  * How long we intend to store your personal data for
  * The source of the information, if we did not collect the data directly from you
  * If you believe that we hold any incomplete or inaccurate data about you, you have the right to ask us to correct and/or complete the information and we will strive to update/correct it as quickly as possible.

Your also have the right to request erasure of your personal data, “your right to be forgotten” or to restrict processing in accordance with local and international data protection laws, as well as to object to any direct marketing from us, and to be informed about any automated decision-making that we use.

If we receive a request for any of the above rights, we may ask you to verify your identity before acting on the relevant request; this is to ensure that your data is protected and kept secure. We will never ask you for sensitive personal data (such as individual identity number, social security number). Should you ever need support with any online account services, we will never ask you for your individual user account password.

We encourage you to keep your personal settings and personal data complete and current.

### SHARING AND DISCLOSING YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We do not share or disclose any of your personal information without your consent, other than for the purposes specified in this notice, where there is a legal requirement or to enforce our security protections, or our terms and conditions. Catapult Systems does not transfer your personal data across extra-territorial boundaries and we will always ask for consent prior to doing so if this becomes a requirement.

We utilize the following processors/controllers who act on our behalf to provide the business functions and services. They act in accordance with specific instructions from us and comply fully with this and their own privacy notice, the local and international data protection laws, and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

### CONSEQUENCES OF NOT PROVIDING YOUR DATA

You are not obligated to provide your personal information to Catapult Systems, however, as it is required so that we can meet our business obligations, we will be unable to provide you with our services without it.

### PROTECTING YOUR PERSONAL DATA

Catapult Systems takes your privacy very seriously and we take every reasonable measure and precaution to protect and secure your personal data. We work to protect you and your information from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction and have several layers of security measures in place, including secure hosting of our website, virus and malware protections, using an SSL certificate, and securing access to our sited via appropriate security controls and systems.

### WHO WE ARE

Catapult Systems (‘we’ or ‘us’ or ‘our’) operates multiple United States regional business offices out of our North American headquarters located at 1221 South MoPac Expressway, Three Barton Skyway, Suite 350, Austin, Texas, 78746, United States of America under DUNS Number: 143983323. We are registered in several US States as a for-profit business under the above DUNS Number and United States under our US Federal Taxpayer Identification Number (TIN): 20-0547052. Catapult acts as the Data Controller in the collection, use, storing, protection and transfer of your personal information. The person in charge of ensuring your data protection rights is Mindy Russell and can be contacted at 512.328.8181 or via [m.russell@catapultsystems](mailto:m.russell@www.catapultsystems.com).

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy. Should this policy substantially change, we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site. If you have any comments, questions or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy, please email us at [privacy@www.catapultsystems.com](mailto:privacy@www.catapultsystems.com) or send your written response to our designated Data Privacy Representative below.

 **Catapult**  
Data Privacy Representative  
1221 South MoPac Expressway,  
Three Barton Skyway, Suite 350  
Austin, Texas, 78746, United States of America  
512.328.8181

 **United States Data Privacy Enforcement Authority**  
U.S. Department of Commerce  
EU-U.S. Privacy Shield  
1401 Constitution Avenue, N.W., Room 20001  
Washington, D.C. 20230
